http://www.gonzagabulletin.com/site/privacy.html

Spokane, WA
(99258)
Today
Partly cloudy skies this evening will give way to occasional snow showers overnight. Low 28F. Winds light and variable. Chance of snow 60%..
Tonight
Partly cloudy skies this evening will give way to occasional snow showers overnight. Low 28F. Winds light and variable. Chance of snow 60%.
Dining Guide
THE GONZAGA BULLETIN PRIVACY POLICYThis Privacy Policy governs the collection of any personal and non-personal information provided to The Gonzaga Bulletin website, whether accessed through computer, tablet, smartphone or other device (individually or collectively) and our mobile applications. If you have any questions or comments regarding this policy please contact us by sending an e-mail to gonzagabulletin@zagmail.gonzaga.edu Collection and Use of personal informationYou do not need to provide any personal information that identifies you to use the Gonzaga Bulletin site. In general, you can visit the Gonzaga Bulletin site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information.However, if you want to use certain online services, you may be asked to provide some personal information, such as your name or e-mail address. We also may ask you to choose a user name and password and provide that information when accessing certain online features. If you do not want to give us any personal information, you can always decide not to use the services. The choice is yours. We are only interested in offering you convenient online services that match your interests and needs.Some examples of when you may voluntarily provide personal information are:E-News. You can register to receive notifications from The Gonzaga Bulletin. In order to provide you with these e-mail notifications, we will ask you to provide certain personal information, such as a user name and e-mail address.Comments. You may comment on the stories on the Gonzaga Bulletin site, however you will need to create a user account. We will ask for your name and email to create this account.Submit News. You may submit news stories to the Gonzaga Bulletin. We will ask for your name, city, state, phone number and email to provide this service.Classifieds. You may purchase classified advertising through the Gonzaga Bulletin website. To purchase classified advertising, we will ask you to provide your name, email address, phone number, address, city, state, zip and payment information.The above list contains the most common instances, but not all instances when the Gonzaga Bulletin website may collect your personal information.Use and Disclosure of Personal and Non-personal InformationThe Gonzaga Bulletin website uses your personal information for one general purpose, to provide you with the services you request.The Gonzaga Bulletin and its service provider, Town News may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Gonzaga Bulletin website. These companies may collect non-personal information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to the Gonzaga Bulletin website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to the Gonzaga Bulletin website, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie* on your browser.Cookies and online tracking technologies*Explanation of cookies and online tracking of non-personal information.Cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that a website places on the hard drive of your computer when you visit the website. Cookies may involve the transmission of information from us to you and from you directly to us, to another party on our behalf, or to another party in accordance with its privacy policy. We may use cookies to bring together information we collect about you. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won’t have access to many features that make your guest experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.Flash cookies. We may use local shared objects, sometimes known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Our advertisers and third-party service providers also may use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. Learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies. If you disable Flash cookies, you won’t have access to many features that make your guest experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.Web beacons. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of sites. Web beacons may involve the transmission of information directly to Town News or to another party on our behalf.Terms, Changes and QuestionsBy using The Gonzaga Bulletin website, you signify your agreement to the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with these terms, please do not use or disclose any personal information on this site.  Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted here, so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. If you have any questions or comments about this policy or our use of personal information, you may send an e-mail to gonzagabulletin@zagmail.gonzaga.edu or send a letter to the following address:The Gonzaga BulletinAtt: Student Media Staff502 E. Boone Ave., Ad Box 94Spokane, Washington 99258
Information Pages
About Us
Advertising
Contact Us
Employment Opportunities
Our Letters Policy
Online Comment Policy
Privacy Policy
GU Office of Sustainability offers free bike lockers for students
1 hr ago
Home for the Holidays with a twist: "Happiest Season" movie review
1 hr ago
Phoebe Bridgers, Taylor Swift & more: Ten outstanding albums of 2020
2 hrs ago
Top 5 movies & TV shows of 2020 that made us forget about Tiger King
6 hrs ago
Gonzaga held BSU Town Hall webinar to address student concerns
Dec 9, 2020
Gonzaga gets gold rating in sustainability from AASHE's tracking
Dec 8, 2020
Popular GU ski spot Schweitzer opens under new COVID regulations
Dec 8, 2020
© Copyright 2020 The Gonzaga Bulletin, 502 East Boone MSC 2476 Spokane, WA | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
